法蘭，我們開會的原因
The whole reason  we do these meetings, Frank,
是我能從你這裏  得到正確的消息
is so I can get  accurate information from you.
我總是說票數會很接近
I always said it was going to be close.
那為什麼我昨晚讀的文章
Then why did every article I read yesterday
都說領導有信心提案會通過？
say the leadership was  confident the bill would pass?
你認識珍妮史柯斯基嗎？
Do you know Janine Skorsky?
她以前是  《先軀報》的白宮記者
She used to be The Herald's  White House correspondent.
我記得珍妮
I remember Janine.
她替《頭條報導》寫的文章  報導確實的票數
She wrote an article for Slugline  reporting a verified vote count.
媒體到手後到處傳
Once the media got ahold of that,  it went everywhere.
我不知道她的數據哪來的  搞不好是編的
I don't know where she got that number.  Maybe she made it up.
那不重要
It doesn't matter if she made it up.
民主黨感覺有點分裂  領導看來很無能
The Democrats seem divided.  The leadership looks incompetent.
但相較於預算和教育提案
But compared to the budget  and our Education Act,
這是小事
why, this was a minor bill, sir.
現在成為全國關注的事
That happened to be  in the national spotlight,
這正合你意
which is what you wanted.
我誤算了票數
I got the count wrong.
很少發生這種狀況  但是確實會發生
It rarely happens, but it happens.
我擔心的是白宮的影響力
See, what worries me is that  the White House's influence
無法轉換成國會的實質支持
isn't translating into support on the Hill.
琳達涉入也不奏效嗎？
Linda's involvement had no effect?
我不會這麼解讀，總統
I wouldn't say that that's the case, sir.
你感覺到教育提案的抵抗  和負面影響嗎？
Did you sense any pushback,  any fallout from the education battle?
總統，事實上我人不在場
Sir, the truth is I wasn't there.
我得到加州和史丹佛大學  教務長會面，談我兒子的事
I had to make a trip to California to meet  the Provost of Stanford, for my son.
我上周跟你提過
I told you about it last week.
是我的決定，總統  我下的決策
It was my decision, sir.  I made a judgment call
沒有她也能通過提案
that we could pass the bill without her help.
但像這樣票數接近的狀況
But, look, tight votes like this,
你可以不停地分析
you can analyze them to death,
但最後結論是我們票數不夠
but at the end of the day, we came up short.
是我的錯，不關任何人的事  絕對不是琳達的責任
That's my fault, no one else's.  Certainly not Linda's.
我不應該去的  會面根本沒用
I shouldn't have gone.  The meeting didn't even work.
你不是說他們打算重新考慮
I thought you said they were reconsidering.
我今早接到電郵
No. I got an email this morning.
他們決定不改變  先前的錄取決定
They decided not to overturn  the admissions decision.
- 天啊，抱歉，琳達  - 今天諸事不順
-Christ. I'm sorry, Linda.  -Yeah. Not a great day so far.
但我很感謝你剛替我說話
But I appreciate your covering for me  in there.
琳達的厄運  或許能成為我的轉機
There may be a way to turn  Linda's bad luck into my good fortune.
但我得先解決倒戈的人們
But first, I must deal  with treason within the ranks,
那兩個投反對票的叛徒
the two renegades  who voted against the bill.
我無法容忍背叛
I have zero tolerance for betrayal,
他們馬上就會知道
which they will soon indelibly learn.
我知道你為何少票
I know why you lost the vote.
有人收買了文德柏與亞柏斯
Somebody got to Vanderburgh and Abrams.
瑞米丹頓
Remy Danton.
你老婆
Your wife.
他們倆個身邊都有我的眼線
I've got contacts on both their staffs.
他們三人曾經會面
There was a meeting  between the three of them.
我知道，是我安排的
I know. I arranged it.
- 她跟他們說投反對票  - 不是這樣
-She told them to vote no.  -No, not true.
兩邊的線民說詞都一致？
Sources on two different staffs  saying the exact same thing?
這不合理
That makes no sense.
我不是告訴你什麼是合理  只是闡述事實
I'm not telling you what makes sense,  I'm telling you facts.
這可是大新聞，法蘭斯
This is a juicy story, Francis.
卡莉一定會愛死的
Carly will love it.
多數黨黨鞭的老婆  在背後捅他一刀
The Majority Whip's wife  stabs him in the back.
小心點，喬伊
Be careful, Zoe.
我爆料給你了  現在換你爆料給我
I'm feeding you. Now you have to feed me.
給我更好的消息
So give me something better.
你到底回不回答我？
Are you going to answer my question?
她有還是沒有？
Did she or didn't she?
最好馬上告訴我
Tell me now, or so help me God,
不然我將全力毀了  你們的政治生涯
I will make it my mission in life  to not only destroy your careers,
奪走你們生命中  所有的希望和快樂
but to obliterate all hope and happiness  that you manage to cling to.
- 她說我們可以…  - 在背後捅我？
-She said it would be okay...  -To backstab me?
做我們認為是對的選擇
To do what we thought was right.
所以她確實要你們投反對票
So she did tell you to vote no.
她說就算不通過  也不會是世界末日
She said it wouldn't be  the end of the world if the bill failed.
她確實是這麼說的
Those were her exact words.
這件事不准傳出這房間  明白嗎？
You discuss this with no one.  Is that understood?
你會為自己不能在華府  親自拉票感到自責嗎？
Do you blame yourself for not being  in Washington to secure the votes?
這麼龐大的提案需要團隊的努力  有許多人背書
A bill this size is a team effort.  There were a lot of sponsors.
你是提案的  主要贊助人和管理人
But you were the chief sponsor  and the bill manager.
- 沒錯  - 你人不應該在華府嗎？
-That's true.  -So shouldn't you have been in Washington?
我正在競選州長  我必須要給我的州民交代
I'm running for governor. I have  a commitment to the people of my state.
你知道史沃佛特競選處
Are you aware that the Swofford campaign
今天公佈一則新廣告
is putting out  a new commercial today that says,
說若彼得魯索在國會做事  都虎頭蛇尾
quote, if Peter Russo can't  follow through in Congress,
他能徹底戒酒嗎？
can he follow through with sobriety?
好了，非常感謝你們
That's all. Thank you very much.
- 你要回應嗎？  - 謝謝各位
-Do you want to comment?  -Thanks, guys.
議員！
Congressman!
我只不過是重複你常講的  要跟著良心投票
All I said was what you always say,  to vote their conscience.
你鼓勵他們忤逆我
You encouraged them to defy me.
我應你的要求和他們會面…
I met with them. That's what you asked me...
你沒有這麼做
No, that is not what you did.
我特別交待你  我需要他們支持這提案
I specifically told you I needed them  to vote yes on this bill.
我表示得非常清楚
There was no room for interpretation.
你刻意欺騙  別再狡辯了，克萊兒
It's a deliberate lie,  so don't try to sugarcoat it, Claire.
我需要瑞米的幫助  你見死不救
I needed Remy's help.  You wouldn't offer any.
等等
Wait.
你這麼做是為了瑞米？
You did this for Remy?
不，是為了我  讓我能在蘇丹出貨
No. For myself.  To get my shipment out of Sudan.
他提供協助
He provided assistance.
用提案失敗作為交換條件
In exchange for defeating the bill.
是協助提案不通過
No. In exchange for not helping it succeed.
還不是一樣
Which is the same goddamn thing.
你知道你危害
Do you realize you have endangered
我們所有的努力嗎？
everything that we have  been working toward?
這是有時間表的，克萊兒
There was a timetable here, Claire.
我們需要堅持到最後一刻
We needed strong momentum  right up until the last minute.
我沒辦法遵守  一個你未告知我的計劃
I can't operate based on plans  you haven't shared with me.
那你應該先詢問我
Then you should've asked me first.
我沒法每個決定  都來要求你同意，法蘭斯
No, I'm not going to ask for your blessing  on every decision I make, Francis.
我們一起做決定
We make decisions together.
感覺不像  至少這半年來都不像
Yeah, well, it hasn't felt like that.  Not for the past six months.
我根本不覺得  我和你並肩作戰
I don't feel as though  I'm standing beside you.
有外人知道了，克萊兒
Other people know, Claire.
這可能轉變成我們的八卦
This could become a story about us.
這樣的損害是沒法復原的
And that's something  you do not recover from.
- 誰？  - 這可會跟人一輩子
-Who?  -That's something that follows you for life.
誰知道？
Who knows?
喬伊
Zoe.
你不是說可以信得過她
I thought you said she could be trusted.
- 我們之間的信任呢？  - 你操控不了她嗎，法蘭斯？
-What about our trust?  -You can't control her, can you, Francis?
你若沒撒謊  她就不會是問題
She wouldn't have been a problem  if you hadn't lied.
你要是沒脫褲子的話  她就不會是問題
No, she wouldn't have been a problem  if you hadn't dropped your pants.
你還有臉  到我的辦公室來指責我
And you come in here, to my office,  and berate me
從頭到尾  都是你掀我們的底？
when you're the one who's exposed us?
別想將錯推到我身上
Don't you try to turn this around on me.
我為了我們炒掉一半的員工
I fired half of my staff for us.
我拒絕了捐款
I have turned down donations for us.
我替彼得寫提案
I drafted Peter's bill for us.
我拋下我的目標  全心全意為了我們
I diverted time and energy  away from my goals for us.
我不想這麼說  但或許你該聽聽
Okay, I don't wanna have to say this,  but maybe you need to hear it.
淨水創權固然重要
CWl is important, yes,
但跟我們想要完成的相比  是小巫見大巫
but it doesn't come close  to what we are trying to accomplish.
你不可能看不出來吧！
You must see that!
我只是據實以報
I'm just being honest.
那不也老實說  你一直在利用我
Then be honest about  how you've been using me
就像你利用所有人一樣
just like you use everybody else.
我們當初根本沒有這樣協議
That was never part of the bargain.
是潮熱嗎？
Is it the hot flashes?
出去
Get out.
家裏見
I'll see you back at the house.
我在路上
I'm on my way to the office.
- 到辦公室後打給你  - 我們要立即談
-Let me call you when I get there.  -No, no. We need to talk now.
我知道你很氣，彼得  但這樣成不了事
I know you're upset, Peter,  but that's not going to achieve anything.
我不只是氣，法蘭
I am more than upset, Frank.
注意你的口氣  我現在沒心情吃這套
Change your tone. I'm in no mood.
- 我才不在乎！  - 再見，彼得
-I don't give a fuck!  -Goodbye, Peter.
你現在若掛我電話  就別怪我下通打給誰
You hang up on me now,  you're not gonna appreciate who I call next.
- 什麼？  - 我答應創造就業機會
-Excuse me?  -I promised my people jobs.
你承諾這提案會聽過
You promised me  you could get this bill passed.
你食言，我可不行
You failed on your promise.  I'm not gonna fail on mine.
所以你最好給我想辦法搞定
So however you need to fix it,  you figure it out.
不然我就抖出羅伊卡普奈  和凱恩社論那件事
Otherwise, I go public with  Kapeniak and the Kern editorial.
你需要冷靜  好好想想你剛才說的話
You need to cool down and think  very carefully about what you just said.
你不懂，我不怕你了，法蘭
You don't understand.  I'm not afraid of you anymore, Frank.
- 那你就錯了  - 我的過去攤在陽光下
-Then you're misguided.  -My past is out in the open.
你已經沒有把柄了
You don't hold that over my head anymore.
他們不知道所有事，彼得
They don't know everything, Peter.
你毀了我，就等於自我毀滅
You destroy me, you destroy yourself.
搞定這件事
Fix it.
- 要我怎麼做？  - 步調要快一點
-What do you want me to do?  -We have to accelerate things.
時機不會太早？  選舉已經開始快兩個月了
Isn't it too early?  It's almost two full months into the election.
白宮要調查時間也太久了
That gives the White House  too much time to vet somebody.
彼得越界了
Peter's crossed the line.
我們給了他點自信  他就不受控制了
We built up his confidence,  and now we're losing control of him.
或許只是發洩罷了
Maybe he was just blowing off steam.
不，他很堅持  我們必須有所行動
No. He's determined. We have to act now.
你那邊需要的都搞定了嗎？
You have everything you need in your end?
隨時隨地都可以開始
Give me a when and a where.
找個社交場合比較好
Some sort of social setting is preferable.
- 還有嗎？  - 我需要現金
-Anything else?  -I'll need cash.
差不多三千
About 3 grand.
明早會放進最上面的抽屜
It'll be in your top drawer  by tomorrow morning.
議員
Sir.
- 一旦開始，就必須貫徹  - 我明白
-Once we do this, we're committed.  -Understood.
- 我無法預料他的反應  - 我不會被要脅
-I can't predict how he's gonna react.  -Well, I won't be blackmailed.
是誰？
Hello?
喬伊邦斯嗎？
Zoe Barnes?
我是，哪位？
Yeah. Who is it?
克萊兒安德沃
Claire Underwood.
喬伊？
Zoe?
很抱歉沒在樓下按鈴
I apologize for not buzzing.
我在樓下時剛好有人進來
Somebody was coming  in the building when I was downstairs,
我就想說…
so I just figured...
這很好啊，逃生梯
This is nice. Fire escape.
請別翻我東西
Hey, could you please  not go through my things?
抱歉，我打擾到你了嗎？
I'm sorry. Am I intruding?
確實是
Yeah, actually. You are.
這樣算扯平了吧
Well, that makes it  a two-way street, I suppose.
若你…是來懲罰我的
Okay, if you...  If you came here to punish me.
我明白
Fine. I get it.
太可惜了
Such a shame.
你太天真了
How naive you are.
我才不天真
I'm not naive.
沒有嗎？
No?
我早就知道了，喬伊
I've known everything  from the beginning, Zoe.
我老公跟我之間沒有秘密
My husband and I tell each other everything.
你不相信我？
Don't you believe me?
有蜘蛛需要我抓嗎？
Is there a spider I can trap?
我不是來懲罰你  也不是來要你停止
I'm not here to punish you  or to tell you to stop.
我只是想讓你看清事實
I just thought I should open  those big bright eyes.
你該走了
I think you should leave.
我也這麼覺得
I think I should, too.
或許你真沒那麼天真
Maybe you're not that naive.
膽小的女人連門都不敢開
A lesser woman  wouldn't have opened the door.
麻煩到聯合車站
Union Station, please.
我是克萊兒  現在無法接聽電話
This is Claire.  I'm unavailable to answer the phone,
但若你留言  我會盡快回覆，謝…
but if you leave a message, I'll be sure  and get back to you shortly. Thank...
- 喂？  - 喬伊
-Hello?  -Zoe.
你不用躡手躡腳的
You don't have to tiptoe.
我以為你睡了
I thought you fell asleep.
沒有，在想工作的事
No. Just thinking about work.
我現在還沒有新消息  但馬上就會有了
I don't have anything for you yet.  I will soon.
我知道
I know you will.
你可以在這過夜
You can spend the night if you want.
明天一早要開會
Early meetings.
沒時間回家換衣服
Wouldn't have time to get home and change.
- 你好像有心事  - 最近煩心的事很多
-You seem distracted.  -I have a lot on my mind.
例如？
Like what?
- 工作，跟你一樣  - 不是克萊兒？
-Work, just like you.  -No Claire?
或許她也算是公事
Or maybe she qualifies as work.
她什麼都沒說？
She didn't mention anything?
關於…
About...
我還以為  你們倆之間沒有秘密
I thought you didn't  keep things from each other.
想說什麼就直說吧
Look, just say what you want to say.
她幾個小時前才來過
She came by here a few hours ago.
我們小聊了一下
We had a nice little talk.
我不送了
Don't let me keep you.
你該回家好好休息
You should go home, get some rest.
幫我跟克萊兒打聲招呼
Tell Claire I said hi.
克萊兒！
Claire!
我是克萊兒  現在無法接聽電話…
This is Claire.  I'm unavailable to answer...
沃頓家的燈待會就會亮了
The lights in the Wartons' house  will go on in a few moments.
每天6點45分準時亮
They always get up  precisely at 6:45,
也是克萊兒去慢跑的時間
which is just the time that Claire  would be going for her run,
若她在這的話
if she were here.
全都反了
Rebellion on all fronts.
克萊兒、喬伊、魯索
Claire, Zoe, Russo.
我絕對不能被擊垮
I must not lose my resolve.
我將向前行
I will march forward,
就算只剩下
even if I have to do so
我一個人
alone.
看吧？我早說了
See? Told ya.
早安
Good morning.
你好，法蘭
Hi, Frank.
- 你好嗎？  - 很好
-How are you?  -I'm good.
有克萊兒的消息嗎？
Have you heard from Claire?
我收到她的留言
Yeah, I got her message.
- 她怎麼樣？  - 好多了
-How's she feeling?  -A lot better.
很好，她說她整周都請假
Good. She said she'd be gone  for the rest of the week.
- 是流感嗎？  - 應該是吧
-ls it the flu or something?  -Something like that.
我只是來辦公室幫她拿些東西
I just came over to pick up  a few things from her office.
- 我派人送去就好了  - 不用麻煩了
-I could've sent somebody over.  -No. It's no big deal.
我順便要來請你幫個忙
In fact, I also came here to ask you a favor.
你是史丹佛畢業的，對嗎？
You went to Stanford, correct?
- 畢業生代表？  - 沒錯
-Valedictorian?  -Yeah.
你跟教務長熟嗎？
Do you know the Provost?
華倫譚斯多
Warren Tynsdale.
他有時會請我參加募款活動
He flies me out to do fundraising events.
說我是校友典範
Supposedly I'm the poster child for alumni.
讓世界變得更好
Making the world a better place.
很好，因為這事很重要
Well, that is good,  because this is important.
總統的參謀，琳達瓦克斯
Linda Vasquez, the President's Chief of Staff,
她兒子魯班申請你們學校
her son, Ruben, applied.
我想請你打個電話給譚斯多
I'd love for you to  get on the phone with Tynsdale
幫我關說
and tell him that they should accept him.
我不知道…  我從來沒有推薦過人
I don't know. I...  I've never recommended anyone.
那更好，這樣講話更夠份量
All the better. It'll carry more weight.
我能先和魯班見面嗎？
Can I meet Ruben first?
我不希望琳達知道這件事
I would really prefer that Linda not know.
最好能讓她跟魯班都認為
In fact, it would be better  if both she and Ruben
是魯班自己夠優秀
believed he got in on merit alone.
可以麻煩你  幫我和克萊兒這個忙嗎？
Will you please do this favor  for Claire and me?
也是幫總統
And for the President.
謝謝
Thank you.
對比再強烈一點
More contrast.
我們需要照到他臉部邊緣
We need to catch the edge of his face.
重新剪裁，左邊再裁6公分
Let's re-crop it. Bring it in  a quarter of an inch on the left.
麻煩你
Would you?
一個叫克萊兒的
Somebody named Claire?
瑞米
Remy.
你餓嗎？
You hungry?
我不吃豬肉
I don't eat pork.
什麼時候的事？
When did that happen?
當我們開始  替肉類處理工業遊說後
When we started lobbying  for the meatpacking industry.
弗萊迪，給我半隻
Freddy, half a rack for me,
幫我朋友送點青菜
and some collard greens for my friend here.
不用了，我吃過了
I'm good. I already ate lunch.
馬上來
Half a rack coming up.
我通常不在這裏談公事  這是我的秘密
I don't usually do business here.  This is my little secret.
我希望你別說出去
I'd love it if we could keep it that way.
你不用擔心我會帶客戶來
I don't think you have to worry  about me bringing clients by.
你好像有點緊張，瑞米
You seem tense, Remy.
我猜你是在悶分水嶺提案的事
I assume you're upset  about the Watershed Bill.
不是針對你  你只是奉公行事
Not with you.  You were just doing your job.
但現在我也必須這麼做
But now I have to do mine.
我想跟你合作
I'd like to propose a partnership.
法蘭，我對合作向來很有興趣
I'm always open to partnerships, Frank.
若彼得魯索是  一個支持自然氣的候選人
If Peter Russo were  a pro-natural gas candidate,
對善可工業有多少價值？
how valuable would that be to SanCorp?
分水嶺提案反鑽井
The Watershed Bill is anti-drilling.
彼得支持的是製造就業機會  不是反鑽井
Peter's pro-employment, not anti-drilling.
他只是想將工作機會  帶給他的選民
He just wants to bring  employment to his people,
善可正在新建精煉廠
and SanCorp is building refineries.
大多是就地新建
Mostly on site.
他們願意考慮在費城設廠嗎？
Do you think they would be open  to considering Philadelphia?
我可以談談看  但無法保證些什麼
I can talk with them,  but I can't make any promises.
我不需要保證  只要跟魯索接洽
I don't want any promises.  Just engage with Russo.
給他一點甜頭
You know, give him  a glimmer of good fortune.
法蘭，你的餐點
Frank, here you go.
你聞聞看
Come on. Smell that.
確定不改變戒豬肉的立場？
You sure you don't want to  reconsider your stance on pork?
補腦，兄弟
Brain food, brother.
- 我好喜歡  - 850元
-I love it.  -$850.
你買得起？
You can afford that?
應該可以
Yeah. Yeah, I think so.
第一個月跟最後一個月  已經付了
First and last month are taken care of.
押金也給了
So is the security deposit.
這些拿去買傢俱
That's to buy some furniture.
我發誓我一定會還你的
I'll pay you back. I promise.
不用了
It's not necessary.
但我需要你幫我一個忙
But I do need you to do one thing for me.
- 這讓我看來像騙子  - 你需要就業機會
-I'd come across as a hypocrite.  -You need jobs.
怎麼製造有差嗎？
Do you really care how you deliver them?
首先，我支持分水嶺  更嚴格管控
First, I advocate for more  regulation for the watershed,
然後再跟鑽井公司合作？
then I cozy up to the drilling interests?
自然氣就是未來，彼得
Yeah, but natural gas is the future, Peter.
這個產業在未來的十年裏
This is an industry  that could bring 100,000 jobs
能為你的州  帶來十萬個就業機會
into your state over the next decade.
我贊同彼得的說法  這樣很像牆頭草
I agree with Peter.  It seems like flip-flopping.
正是因為善可工業的遊說  分水嶺提案才沒有過
SanCorp's lobbying efforts is  why we lost the Watershed Bill.
但他們也可以是  很強大的盟友
But they can also be  a very powerful ally.
我們強調的是「重新開始」
Our message is "A fresh start."
這讓人覺得  「一切還是照常運作」
This makes you look like  "Business as usual."
這是政治
This is politics.
其中有把握住的機會  和錯過的機會
There are seized opportunities  and missed opportunities.
把握這次機會，彼得
Seize this one, Peter.
善可工業能承諾  會在費城設廠嗎？
SanCorp can commit to  building new refineries in Philly?
善可工業會承諾  跟你談這件事
SanCorp will commit  to discussing it with you.
- 這樣不夠  - 你要我幫你解決問題
-I need more than that.  -Look, you asked me to fix a problem.
我在24小時內  就捧著解決之道過來
I've come to you in less than  24 hours with a solution.
能不能幫幫忙？
Can you meet me halfway?
第一步是什麼呢？
What would be the first step?
你還記得瑞米丹頓嗎？
All right.  You remember Remy Danton?
拜託，就是他帶頭  反對分水嶺提案
Come on. He led the charge  against the Watershed Bill.
我知道，這不是重點
I know. That's not the point.
他的另一個大客戶  是麥尼力癌癥研究所
One of his other big clients is  the McNeally Cancer lnstitute.
他們今晚為捐贈者  舉辦一場慈善晚會
They're having a big gala tonight,  a cocktail party for their donors.
瑞米會出席
Remy will be there.
哈弗福德和葛萊溫有活動
We have events in Haverford and Gladwyne.
這比較重要
Yeah, well, this is more important.
明早不是跟匹茲堡  當地電台有專訪嗎？
You also have a radio interview tomorrow  morning with a local Pittsburgh station?
- 對  - 很好
-Yes.  -All right.
今晚跟瑞米碰面
Meet with Remy tonight.
若一切順利的話
And if it goes well and ifyou're comfortable,
明早專訪時  你就支持他們鑽井
tomorrow morning on the radio,  you support their drilling efforts.
瑞米答應我只要你這麼做
And Remy has assured me if you do that,
他就能說服善可工業
he can push SanCorp in the right direction.
明天的活動取消
Cancel the events tomorrow.
回費城控制一下場面
Head back to Philly,  do some damage control.
- 我們明天下午見  - 彼得…
-I'll see you tomorrow afternoon.  -Peter...
拜託
Please.
好吧
Okay.
我有些電話要打
I'm gonna go make some calls.
彼得，你有跟她提過  卡普奈或…
Peter, have you mentioned anything  to her about Kapeniak or...
我沒跟任何人提過
No. I haven't mentioned it to anybody.
好吧，史坦普明早會過來
All right.  Stamper will come by in the morning
跟你匯報勸說重點
and briefyou on the talking points.
這張什麼時候照的？
When did you take this?
早上7點左右吧
It was about 7:00 in the morning.
太陽才剛升起
The sun had just come up.
你就睡在那裏
You were asleep right here.
燈光恰好
The light was perfect.
我沒選擇
I had no choice.
我每次在這裏都睡得很安穩
I always slept so well in this apartment.
你這次待多久？
How long are you in town for?
不知道
I don't know.
我還沒決定
I haven't decided.
你沒有行李
You have no luggage.
這裏味道還是沒變
It smells the same.
感覺也沒變
Feels the same.
善可工業不在費城發展
I think SanCorp is missing out,
是他們的損失
not having a significant  presence in Philadelphia.
集中在這樣的大都市  有許多利處
There are advantages to centralizing  in a major urban center.
但弊處包括商業地產的價格
But the disadvantages are  commercial real estate prices,
市政課稅、政治管道
city taxes, political pipeline.
這些都很花錢
It's all very costly.
就必須從別的地方削減
So they'd have to reduce costs elsewhere.
- 大幅度削減  - 我能幫得上忙嗎？
-Significantly.  -How can I help with that?
全州許可使用分區
Statewide permitted use zoning.
不再是管制分區
No more conditional zoning.
市政府都在延緩發展
The municipalities  are slowing down development.
那是州議會的決策
That's the state legislature.
你公開支持許可使用  還當選州長
You come out in support of permitted use,  and you get elected governor.
這樣就可以對州議會施壓
That'll put pressure on the legislature.
善可工業很想在哈利遜堡  交到有權勢的朋友
SanCorp is very interested in having  a powerful friend in Harrisburg.
我的對手支持鑽井
My opponent's pro-drilling.
你的對手沒有讓精煉廠進費城
Your opponent isn't asking  for refineries in Philadelphia.
我們喜歡靠得住的朋友
We prefer friends we can count on.
要你的客戶明早7點45分  收聽WZPZ電台
Have your clients listen to WZPZ  tomorrow at 7:45.
那是匹茲堡的電台
It's a Pittsburgh station.
幸會，議員
It's been a pleasure, Congressman.
我很期待再跟你聊天
I look forward to talking again soon.
有火嗎？
You got a light?
這是癌癥研究的晚會
This is a cancer research event.
我知道，我是協辦人
I know. I helped organize it.
- 你是研究所的人？  - 我是飯店人員
-You work for the institute?  -No. The hotel.
他們讓你在這裏抽煙？
And they let you smoke here?
不，經理會殺了我
No. The manager would kill me.
但至少能讓你開口
Well, at least it got you talking.
你還盡興嗎？看來很開心
Are you having a good night?  You look happy.
我是啊，我今晚很開心
I am. I am.  I'm having a great night.
- 為什麼？  - 剛剛聽到好消息
-Why?  -I just got some very good news.
我們應該慶祝，你喝什麼？
We should celebrate.  What are you drinking?
其實我正打算要離開
You know, I was just leaving, actually.
你連我的名字都沒有問？
You haven't even asked my name yet.
- 抱歉，但我真的得走了  - 是瑞秋
-I apologize, but I have to go.  -It's Rachel.
不是刻意無禮  只是明早有重要會議
I'm not trying to be rude,  but I got a big meeting tomorrow.
那就別無禮，就留個幾分鐘
Then don't be rude.  Just stay a few more minutes
別逼我去社交
and keep me from having to mingle.
我的伴丟下我
My date ditched me.
所以若你現在也落跑  真的很無禮
So if you abandon me now,  that would be very rude.
穿這鞋腳真痛
These heels are killing me.
- 你摸摸看，都起泡了  - 我…
-Feel that. Feel that blister.  -Hey, l...
我有女朋友了
I have a girlfriend.
沒有的話才奇怪吧
I'd be surprised if you didn't.
- 你的伴為何丟下你？  - 很八卦
-Why'd your date ditch you?  -Very scandalous.
怎麼了？
What happened?
跟我碰杯
Clink glasses with me.
嘩
Wow.
我個子雖小，但很能喝
I'm petite, but I can hold my liquor.
看得出來
Obviously.
但是我要是喝醉…
When I do get drunk, though...
怎樣？
What then?
就會脫衣服
I get undressed.
你呢？
What about you?
你喝醉時喜歡做什麼？
What are you like when you get drunk?
- 可不好看  - 好看有什麼了不起
-It's not pretty.  -Pretty's overrated.
我喜歡有點醜陋的東西
I like it when things get a little bit ugly.
我加班時  飯店會供應房間給我
When I work late nights,  they let me stay at the hotel
這樣就不用開車回家
so I don't have to drive home.
這是你的
This one is yours.
1121房
Room 1121.
- 議員？  - 在這裏
-Sir?  -ln here.
有事找我？
You wanted to see me?
我需要你幫我找個人
I need you to locate somebody.
誰？
Who?
我老婆
My wife.
有辦法嗎？
Do you have a way of doing that?
有的，議員
I do, sir.
我在失蹤人口組有認識人
I know a guy, Missing Persons.
她沒有失蹤，我只是
She's not missing. I just
不知道她現在在哪裏
don't know where she is at the moment.
我信任他
I trust him.
我們可以私下搞定
We can do this off the books.
很好
Good.
我馬上去辦
I'll get on it right away.
- 再來一個  - 不要，我告訴你為什麼
-Come on. Give us another one.  -No. I'll tell you why.
因為我媽以前老是要我多笑
Because my mother always  used to tell me to smile more.
我覺得好煩，她會說
Always drove me crazy. She'd say,
「克萊兒  你為何老是臭著一張臉？
"Claire, why have you that scowl all the time?
「你笑起來漂亮多了」
"You look so much more beautiful  when you smile."
從來沒有關心
It was never a real conversation.
從來沒有說：  「你好嗎？」  或「你在想些什麼？」
There was never, "What do you feel?"  Or "What are you thinking?"
只要我每天看來漂漂亮亮  開開心心就好
Just so long as I looked beautiful and happy.
她只在乎這點
That's all she cared about.
所以你是要我問  你在想些什麼？
So you want me to ask you  what you're thinking and feeling?
隨時隨地
All the time.
可是我真的想知道  你到底在想什麼
I actually do wanna know what  you're thinking and feeling.
- 我真的好遜  - 先跟我說
-How sad am l?  -Okay, so tell me first.
- 什麼？  - 先告訴我
-What?  -Tell me first.
- 我應該先穿衣服  - 什麼？為什麼？
-I think I'd better get dressed.  -What? Why?
因為…
Because...
我有朋友要來
I've got friends coming over,
做主人的應該要衣衫整齊
and as a host,  I should probably wear clothes.
- 真的？  - 對
-Really?  -Yeah.
- 為什麼要這樣？  - 你也知道
-Why do you do that?  -Well, you know.
- 禮儀？  - 對啊
-It's proper?  -Kind of.
該死
Fuck.
我以為你落跑了
Thought you might have bailed.
坐下
Sit down.
伏特加還是威士忌？
Vodka or whiskey?
你喝吧
You go ahead.
拜託，在樓下乖就算了  上來可不准
Come on. You can be  a good boy downstairs, not up here.
真的，不用了
Seriously, I'm good.
威士忌吧
Whiskey, I think.
你說的好消息是？
So what's your good news?
我要知道我們為何要慶祝
I wanna know what we're celebrating.
你的伴…  你的伴為何丟下你？
Why did your...  Why did your date ditch you?
- 我先問你的  - 是我在樓下先問的
-I asked you first.  -I did, downstairs.
他在國會工作
He works on the Hill.
內部職員吧
Some staffer or something.
我也不知道  我想他應該是跑腿小弟
I don't know.  I think he's a glorified gofer.
朋友介紹我們認識的
A friend set me up with him.
我跟他說他今晚應該來陪我
So I said he should come tonight,  keep me company.
但他卻只顧著拍馬屁
But all he wanted to do was schmooze.
所以我把他帶進女廁
So I brought him  into the women's bathroom,
跟他說他是個混蛋
told him he was being an asshole.
他說我太幼稚  所以我就給了他一巴掌
He told me I was being childish.  So I slapped him.
你甩他巴掌？
You slapped him?
他臉上好紅的五指印
Yeah. Big red hand mark  right across his face.
他應該是覺得  被那些大咖看到很丟臉
I think he was embarrassed  to be seen by the schmoozerati.
所以就走了
So he left.
這是我最後一次  跟佩帶國旗徽章的人約會
And that is the last time I go on a date  with a guy who wears a flag pin to work.
我也是佩帶那種徽章  去上班的人
I'm one of those guys  who wears a flag pin to work.
這不算是約會吧？
This isn't really a date, is it?
我真的不該在這裏
I really shouldn't be here.
所以才好玩啊
That's what makes it fun.
告訴我你的好消息  這樣我才知道為何乾杯
Tell me your good news.  I wanna know what we're toasting to.
為你吧
Let's toast to you.
我就是你的好消息？  好，就為這乾杯
I'm your good news?  Okay, I'll toast to that.
等等
Hey.
你在…
What are you...
我不想在《先軀報》那裏等
I didn't wanna wait at The Herald.
我本來要打給你，但是…
I was gonna call you, but...
今晚可以睡你那裏嗎？
Can I stay at your place tonight?
睡我那裏？
Stay with me?
就借你家沙發一、兩天
Well, just on your couch for a night or two.
- 為什麼？  - 我不能待在我家
-Why?  -I can't be in my apartment.
- 發生什麼事嗎？  - 沒事，我…
-Did something happen?  -No. I...
抱歉
I'm sorry.
喬伊
Zoe.
走吧
Come on.
專訪是什麼時候？
What time is the interview?
7點45分，我會跟他一起
7:45. I'll be with him.
彼得現在人呢？
And where's Peter now?
你確定要知道細節？
Are you sure you want the details?
說吧，一切順利嗎？
Just tell me, is it going well?
還沒有聽到消息
Hasn't been any updates.
若順利，你準備好了嗎？
But if it does go well, you'll be ready?
我一直都準備好了
I'm ready.  I've been ready. I'm ready.
- 還有什麼嗎？  - 我倆沒下過棋，對嗎？
-Anything else?  -We never played chess before, have we?
我不會
I don't know how.
要我教你嗎？
You want me to teach you?
我該去休息了  明早才會有精神
I should really get some rest.  Be fresh for the morning.
下次吧
Yeah, another time.
1160AM、WZPZ電台  7點45分，晚安
1160, WZPZ, 7:45. Good night.
我討厭被蒙在鼓裏
I hate being kept in the dark.
等待
Waiting.
猜測
Speculating.
無用
Useless.
來吧！來跳舞
Come on! Let's dance.
這裏不錯
This is really nice.
要喝什麼嗎？水或果汁？
Do you want anything?  Water? Juice?
不用了，謝謝
No, thanks. I'm good.
床讓給你，我睡沙發
You can have the bed.  I'll sleep on the couch.
不用了
No. No.
不要緊
It's fine.
拜託，盧卡斯  讓我睡沙發，不然我會內疚
Please, Lucas, let me sleep on the couch.  I'll feel bad.
好吧
All right.
- 需要幫忙嗎？  - 我自己來就好
-Could I help?  -I got it.
所以…
So...
你不想說的話  我們可以不談這話題
You know, we don't have to talk  if you don't want to.
我差不多有半年
But I haven't seen you in, like,
沒有見到你了
six months.
除了我喝醉跟蹤你…
Except for when  I drunkenly stalked you at your...
- 對  - 還滿可愛的
-Right.  -That was kind of adorable.
不是瘋了就是很可悲
It was either psychotic or sad.
不可愛
Not adorable.
很可愛
Yes, it was.
枕頭給我，好嗎？
Can you hand me that pillow?
你為何要逃離家裏？
So, why do you need  to get out of your apartment?
感覺好壓迫
It just felt small.
不可能比我家小吧
Well, it can't be smaller than my place.
我不是指空間，而是…
No. I don't mean size. I mean...
感覺被困住了
I felt trapped.
好像身處一個陌生的地方
Like I was in a place  that I didn't actually live.
明白嗎？
Does that make any sense?
好像吧
I guess.
好吧
Okay.
好了
There you go.
需要特定時間起床嗎？還是…
Any time you need to get up? Or...
我用手機設鬧鐘就可以了
I'll just set an alarm on my phone.
好吧，要看電視請自便
All right.  Well, feel free to watch TV.
我多吵都照樣睡
I can sleep through anything.
謝謝你，盧卡斯
Hey, thank you, Lucas.
剩最後一點
Hey, that's the last of it.
那可要用心喝
Better make it count, then.
干了
Drink up.
我看來眼熟嗎？
Do I look familiar to you?
眼熟？不會啊
Familiar? No.
- 我的臉？身體？  - 不會
-My face? My body?  -No.
我的聲音呢？
How about my voice?
我們…
Have we...
沒有
No.
我只是很好奇  你是不是特別喜歡棕髮碧眼的
No. I was just wondering if you had  a thing for brunettes with blue eyes.
- 你去哪裏？回來  - 我想要仔細看你
-Hey, where you going? Come back here.  -I wanna see you better.
天亮了嗎？
Shit. The sun's up?
有一陣子了
Has been for a while.
該死，幾點了？
Fuck. What time is it?
7點15分
7:15.
該死，我半小時後有專訪
Fuck. I have an interview in half an hour.
- 別去了  - 不行，一定要
-Skip it.  -I can't. I gotta do it.
中午才需要退房
You can keep the room till noon.
- 喂？  - 我在你家樓下
-Hello?  -I'm at your building.
管理員一直打給你  可是都沒人接
The front desk keeps calling up,  but there's no answer.
- 我不在家  - 那我去接你，你在哪？
-I'm not there.  -Then I'll come to you. Where are you?
我在帕克哈爾摩飯店
I'm at the Park Highmore Hotel.
你沒事吧  聽起來好像喝醉了
Are you okay? You sound drunk.
這…我沒事
It was... Yeah, yeah. I'm all right.
- 你有專訪  - 我知道！
-You have the interview.  -I know!
你喝酒了嗎，彼得？
Have you been drinking, Peter?
什麼？沒有  我只是留下來過夜
What? No.  I just decided to spend the night here.
你在幾號房？
What room are you in?
11…1121號房
1 1... 1 1 21.
別亂跑，我馬上過來
Stay there. I'm coming right now.
老天，彼得，發生什麼事？  你醉了
Jesus, Peter. What happened?  You're drunk.
- 我沒事  - 我聞得到你身上的酒味
-I'm fine.  -I can smell it on you.
我只喝了幾杯，沒有很誇張
Okay, I had a drink or two.  It was nothing crazy.
我們不能這樣去專訪
We can't do this interview.
我很清醒，我可以的
I'm sober. I can handle it.
你話都講不清楚
You're slurring your words.
我沒事
I'm good.
我們應該取消
I think we should cancel.
我必須要去
I'm gonna do the interview.
把勸說重點給我
Just give me the talking points.
抱歉
Sorry.
抱歉，我…
Sorry. I...
沒關係
It's all right.
沙發的彈簧，我的背…
The couch had a spring in it  or something, and my back...
別說了
Stop.
不要緊
It's all right.
我不介意
I don't mind.
議員，我朋友回覆我了
Sir, I heard from my friend.
失蹤人口組的朋友
Missing Persons.
然後呢？
And?
- 她在紐約  - 哪家飯店？
-She's in New York.  -What hotel?
不是飯店，議員
Not a hotel, sir.
所以她不是一個人？
So she's not alone?
是的，議員
No, sir.
亞當蓋羅威？
Adam Galloway?
是的，議員
Yes, sir.
- 我還有更多情報  - 我不用知道
-I have more information.  -I don't need to know.
轉到1160AM
Turn on 1 160 AM.
他要競選吉姆馬修的舊職位  賓州州長
He's running to fill Jim Matthews' old post  as Governor of Pennsylvania.
很高興你能光臨，議員
Glad to have you with us, sir.
是我的榮幸，吉姆
It's good to be here, Jim.
- 是馬克  - 抱歉，馬克
-It's Mark.  -Sorry. Right. Mark.
不要緊，議員  一大早難免會出錯
That's okay, Congressman. It happens  all the time this early in the morning.
議員，關於分水嶺法案
So, Congressman, the Watershed Act.
是的，我很慚愧…
Yes. I'm ashamed of the...
我不慚愧，這樣說不對…
Well, I'm not ashamed.  That's not the right...
我很失望，因為…
I'm disappointed, because, you know...
水是…
The water is...
是…其實我想討論的是…
It's... Actually, what I'd like to discuss is...
我們都知道自然氣…
We all know that natural gas...
正在成長…在我們的州…
That it's... It's a growing...  In our state...
是…很大一部分…
It's a... It's a big part of...
經濟走向是如此
Economically, the way things are going.
我想要說…想要宣佈…
And I'd like to say...  To announce...
就這來說…
In terms of...
你對鑽井法令熟悉嗎？
Are you familiar with drilling regulations?
許可使用與管制使用？
Permitted use versus conditional use?
我們還在談分水嶺提案嗎？
Are we still talking about the Watershed?
不是，是鑽井、自然氣
No. Drilling. Natural gas.
議員，你原本支持加強管控
Sir, you supported increased regulation.
不是，我…
Well, no. I... I...
看來或許是這樣，但是…
It may have looked that way, but...
確切來說，我支持減少…
In fact, to be clear, I'm for less...
管控
Regulation.
沒錯，議員  分水嶺提案中清楚提到…
Yes, sir. In the Watershed Bill,  the language clearly stated...
提案沒有通過
It didn't pass.
沒錯，我就是想要問這個
Well, right. That's what I'm asking about.
- 怎樣？  - 為何沒有通過？
-What about it?  -Why it didn't pass?
我剛說了
I just said.
議員，你沒有說清楚
No, sir. I don't think you did.
就是沒有通過
It just didn't.
議員，你三天前曾預測…
Sir, three days ago, you predicted...
我在講自然氣的事
I'm talking about fucking natural gas.
- 抱歉  - 議員，我要問你一個問題
-I'm sorry.  -Congressman, I have to ask you a question,
或許你會覺得很失禮
and it may come across as indelicate,
但你現在是喝醉嗎？
but are you drunk right now?
什麼？沒有，我沒事
What? No. No. I'm fine. I'm fine.
我只是很累，明白嗎？
I'm just... I'm really tired, you know?
發給：喬伊  你想要的好戲
我這幾周都在拉票…
I've been on the campaign trail  for a few weeks now...
議員？
Congressman?
議員？議員？
Congressman? Congressman?
是我的錯  我不該讓你接受專訪
It's my fault.  I shouldn't have let you.
我完了
I'm fucked.
聽著，我們先醒酒
Okay. Listen. We sober you up.
盡快發新聞稿
We'll make some kind of  announcement as soon as possible.
我無話可說
There's nothing I can say.
我們一起想辦法
We'll figure this out.
別這樣
Come on.
你該去洗個澡
You're gonna take a shower.
走吧
Come on.
來，過來
There you go. Come on.
有多糟？
How bad is it?
那要看有沒有主流媒體接手
It all depends on whether it gets  picked up by the mainstream press.
- 要跟總統匯報嗎？  - 先緩一緩
-Well, shall I fill in the President?  -No. Hold off on that.
我需要跟彼得聊聊  協調他的競選活動
I need to speak to Peter,  coordinate with his campaign.
我第一個就打給你
You'll be the first call I make.
法蘭，收線之前  我今早收到封電郵
Frank, before you go,  I got an email this morning.
史丹佛改變主意了
Stanford reversed their decision.
太好了
That's wonderful.
教務長說吉莉安柯爾打給他
The Provost said Gillian Cole  reached out to him.
我上網查了她  她是克萊兒的員工
I googled her.  She works for Claire.
- 謝謝你  - 沒理由謝我
-Thank you.  -No reason to thank me.
魯班開心得不得了  我真不知道怎麼報答你
Ruben was just ecstatic.  I don't know how I'm gonna repay you.
你兒子開心就夠了
The fact that your son is happy  is more than enough.
- 彼得有消息再跟我說  - 一定
-You'll keep me posted on Peter?  -You bet.
好
Okay.
老闆
Hey, boss.
- 你還跟他在一起嗎？  - 對
-Are you still with him?  -Yeah.
- 他在洗澡  - 狀況怎麼樣？
-He's taking a shower.  -How're we looking?
喬伊邦斯十分鐘前上傳
Zoe Barnes posted 10 minutes ago.
已經上了《紐約時報》官網
It's already on The New York Times website.
這小子完了
The kid is done.
讓南茜跟副總統安排會面
Have Nancy set up a meeting  with the Vice President.
- 最好能今天  - 知道了
-Today if possible.  -Will do.
看著彼得  他已經完成任務了
And keep an eye on Peter.  He's done his duty.
- 記得幫他重新站起來  - 知道了
-Let's get him back on his feet.  -You got it.
現在輪到吉姆馬修  只是他還不知道罷了
And now Jim Matthews comes to the fore,  though he doesn't know it yet.
他會在他心愛的賓州  找到安慰
He will find solace  in his beloved Pennsylvania,
但彼得魯索卻走投無路
though Peter Russo will find solace nowhere.
要捏碎一個人的野心  只需要十秒鐘
It only takes 10 seconds  to crush a man's ambitions.
我要好好保護自己
I need to take care I protect mine.
彼得
Peter.
彼得！
Peter!
彼得？
Peter?
喂！
Hey!